hey you're on caffeine man here and
today we're going over v8 energy energy
drink that's right we're airing another
healthy energy drink to the healthy
energy drink series and you know it's
gonna be healthy I mean it's v8 I mean
you get 100 percent of your vegetables
and one serving and this one's got fruit
in it as well I think it's 100 percent
servings in regular v8 this is v8 energy
so it might be a little bit different so
do you still get the same amount of
veggies because I think it's a smaller
can as well well when it comes to v8
what oh yeah I forgot something I'll be
right back hello again everybody
ouch that hurt thanks again for joining
me today we're going over v8 energy
energy drink okay I tell you guys
something I hate I mean this stuff
tastes horrible I don't know I don't
know how anybody can drink it I mean it
literally makes me want to puke I mean
is it just for old people because I
don't see any younger people drinking I
don't even see middle-aged people
drinking it so why am i reviewing it I
have no idea
torture but no seriously some of you
guys requested it and since you guys
seem to like the healthy energy drink
reviews I'm bringing another healthy
energy drink review at the risk of my
own taste buds but then when I actually
looked it up and I saw some of the
flavors they actually sound pretty good
so even if they're bad they did a great
job with the marking because they sold
me on it but before I get into that if
you're new to my channel and you want to
stay informed on all things caffeine
related feel free to hit the subscribe
button I post new videos every Tuesday
night also feel free to share me all
over social media I'm on Instagram
Facebook Twitter I'm even on LinkedIn
what really apparently after last week's
video I got one more follower on
LinkedIn so first I'll go over a little
bit about the company then I'll go over
the nutrition facts in the ingredients
that make this healthy and then I'll do
a taste test time stamps in the
description box down below so you can go
exactly where you want to go v8 is an
amazing drink
I mean it's so amazing I'm most puked
the first time I had it I mean I thought
it was bad or it was spoiled or
something bad but no that's just how it
tastes and I know I'm not alone when I
say that something about they're like
yeah why is he doing v8 because it
tastes so bad I know for a fact my
comment box down below is gonna be going
crazy with the people like you're crazy
v8
is the best thing since sliced bread
that's probably what they eat when they
drink it
the truth is it has to be good because
it wouldn't be on the market if it
wasn't selling well so even though my
opinion is it doesn't really taste that
great I'm sure there are plenty of
healthy people out there I love it so
feel free to leave me your comments down
below if you'd love the eight or four
makes you puke so if you didn't know v8
is actually owned by Campbell Soup
Company and they're headquartered in New
Jersey the company was started in 1869
by two people
Joseph Campbell and Abraham Anderson in
1876 Anderson left the partnership and
Arthur dorrance joined the company
dorrance would actually succeed Joseph
Campbell in 1894 they started off with
just tomato soup and they thrived for
many years with just that product alone
it wasn't until 1934 40 years later that
they came out with chicken noodle soup
in cream of mushroom
fast forward to 1948 they established
their v8 brand and we're on their way to
being the leading vegetable juice
company in the United States and as of
today it's still the leader for
vegetable juice of course v8 eventually
needed to add to their line like many
companies do so as time progressed they
expanded out in 1997 they came out with
v8 splash then in 2005 they came out
with their VA fusion which was 100%
vegetable and fruit juice then like so
many other companies out there they saw
the energy market beginning to boom and
they wanted to get a piece of that
market so in 2011 they came out with v8
energy they actually have 15 flavors of
v8 energy if you include their vegetable
juice energy their sparkling energy in
their diet energy flavors I have five of
the most popular flavors to go over with
you today and those flavors are
pomegranate blueberry strawberry banana
peach mango orange pineapple and black
cherry don't lose all sound delicious I
hope so and of course no energy drink
story would be complete without a
lawsuit that's right in February of 2019
not too long ago a lawsuit was filed
against the Campbell Soup Company saying
that if falsely markets that the
caffeine provides a steady energy as
indicated on the can as well as saying
that it's just sweet potato juice and
there aren't any other fruits and
vegetables in there and they say that
they're falsely advertising that there's
no added sugar and of course because a
lawsuit has been filed every uneducated
one is all up in arms about it saying oh
I feel betrayed I feel
Lyde - they're posted in common inboxes
no fruit and v8 sound familiar - no
creatine did this drink stupid without
the case even being in court yet they
just filed a lawsuit listen people just
because someone files a lawsuit against
somebody doesn't automatically make them
guilty at least wait for the results of
the trial before being up in arms about
it energy drink lawsuits are inevitable
for anybody that decides to go into the
energy drink market given the science
behind energy drinks in their tendency
to have mixed results based on who's
doing the scientific study people are
willing to sue anybody over anything
because they might actually have a small
chance at winning depending on who's
doing the study and who the judge is
that day basically we're on product
claims that have provide steady energy
lots of lawyers are ready to pounce on
that situation because that sounds like
an opinion as opposed to scientific fact
they'll argue all day long that science
can't prove that it has a steady energy
because it really seems like it's more
of a personal opinion as we all know
caffeine affects everyone differently
and everyone's bodies are different so
they're definitely gonna be some cases
that say they didn't actually get a
steady energy from the drink and those
are the people the lawyers look for in
their trial it's great to live in a
country where a billion-dollar company
can lie to people just to make an extra
buck yeah even if the company is
actually being honest there's plenty of
dishonest people out there trying to
make an easy buck because they don't
want to lift a finger to work an honest
day or working the whole entire life
what's I just get political yeah which I
hate comments down below I'll delete
them anyway so actually god these drinks
in a six-pack from Target and actually
only cost like four bucks that comes out
to like 66 cents each which isn't bad
for an 8 ounce drink that gives you all
your fruits and vegetables for the day
as well and a whole bunch of caffeine
for energy but wait does it actually
give you all your fruits and vegetables
for the day or am I just thinking that
because it's v8 and and that's one of
their things they say or maybe I just
assumed that's what they say so let's
take a closer look at the can right on
the can this is a black cherry flavored
well actually each one has a different
flavor so it will say that flavor name
with a 50% blend of five vegetable and
fruit juices from concentrate with green
tea extract and other natural flavors it
also states one combined serving of
veggies and fruit and steady energy from
green tea so was that all mean well
one can has two ounces of vegetable
juice and 2 ounces of fruit juice for a
total of four ounces which is half a cup
easy math one serving of vegetables or
fruit is four ounces or half a cup so
this is one serving
that being said dietary supplement
guidelines recommend two and a half cups
of vegetables and two cups of fruit for
a 2,000 calorie diet that means your
daily intake or fruits and vegetables
should be about four and a half servings
so you definitely need more than one can
to get all your daily fruits and
vegetables or you can just eat fruits
and vegetables
either way it's healthy there are
actually three different nutrition fact
panels for these drinks because each one
has different ingredients that give it
different numbers so as you can see the
calories range from 45 to 60 calories
depending on the can they all have zero
fat between 50 and 65 milligrams of
sodium between 11 and 14 total carbs
between 10 to 12 total sugars without
any added sugar and zero protein on to
the vitamins all the vitamins on the can
are the same so you're gonna have 2
percent or your daily value of potassium
10 percent or your vitamin C 25 percent
of your thiamine riboflavin niacin and
b6 and 50% of your b12 not too bad as
for the caffeine this little 8 house
can't has 80 milligrams of caffeine
putting it on par with your average Red
Bull or monster which comes in at 10
milligrams per ounce alright it's time
to taste these things out wish me luck
we're first gonna start out with the
orange pineapple also these are non
carbonated and as some of you may know I
actually like lightly carbonated things
or no carbonated energy drinks so it's a
plus that these aren't carbonated also
the fact that these are actually made
with green tea extract is a good thing
for me as well because I actually like
things with a green tea extract because
they are known for having a steady
energy as opposed to a sugar crash take
that you stupid lawsuit alright I guess
I gotta try I'm just I don't know why
I'm for passing I'm sorry if I'm taking
too long in the video I'm trying to cut
it down let's just do this
okay not too bad I'm pleasantly
surprised that I'm not puking right now
big bonus although some of you guys
probably want to watch me puke didn't ya
didn't ya yeah I mean it's actually a
little bit strange because I'm not
getting a really strong orange or strong
pineapple flavor which is extremely
strange because I'm used to drinking
regular energy drinks and you're usually
hit with that orange I hit with that
pineapple because orange and pineapple
are both relatively strong flavors but
I'm guessing because this is a fruit
juice and a vegetable juice those
flavors a little bit later it doesn't
really taste like a vegetable juice to
me and I can actually taste the
pineapple in the orange a little bit and
I think it's covering up any bad
vegetable taste that I might be used to
from the past
am I gonna recommend these to all my
energy drink friends no no no definitely
not these are not your typical energy
drink these are healthy vegetable fruit
drinks so if you're looking for a
regular energy drink make sure you stick
to my other energy drink reviews if you
looking for something really healthy
really healthy then you're gonna want to
go for something like this because it's
not an energy drink it really is just a
vegetable fruit juice that they added
caffeine to and some B vitamins and some
niacin and some b6 and let's move on to
the next one the next one I'm going on
to the black cherry because I'm hoping
it tastes like soda but I know it's not
going to because it's a vegetable or
fruit juice but we'll see
it's actually not a diet but yeah that's
actually not a bad I can't say bad black
cherry that's actually not a bad black
cherry it still has a little bit of that
vegetable fruit juice flavor but it's
still overpowered by the black cherry
flavor once again it's very different
from all the other energy drinks that
I've had this much more of a vegetable
and fruit drink with a hint of black
cherry but it's definitely not bad
would I ever purchase these on my own
probably not unless like I was in a
hospital they said you need to drink v8
to get better I said can you give me a
v8 energy then please know what doctors
we're not gonna have recommend caffeine
to you say yeah but is v8 energy
caffeine so it's got to be good what am
I talking about
next up is the pomegranate blueberry
that's not too bad either I'm a fan of
blueberry stuff as you guys might know
I'm doing multiple drinks in my taste
test I'm always doing multiple drinks
that's just one who does just one now
caffeine man no no no I never do does
one I a do like five yeah but I usually
try usually start off with the ones I
don't think I'm gonna like as much I
work my way up to the ones that I think
are gonna be the best and this one is
actually pretty good
it's much more of a blueberry drink as
opposed to the vegetable fruit juices
like the other two I still get a hint of
that vegetable fruit juice flavor but
the blueberry and the pomegranate are
pretty decent cover up that healthy
flavor better I'm even gonna risk
another sip not too bad
next up is the peach mango now a lot of
you might be saying wait is that the
last one no this is the fourth one and
those people that watch my videos know
that peach mango is probably my favorite
of all of the energy drinks besides
coconut red ball but peach mango always
tends to show up high on my list so why
am I doing this one second to last
because the last one is strawberry
banana I'm a big fan of strawberry
banana problem is I don't know any
energy drinks they have strawberry
banana
why don't we energy drinks have banana
why have my voice just go really high
right there it just went really high
didn't it
Oh energy drinks must be kicking in but
anyway yeah if you guys know any
strawberry banana energy drinks out
there let me know on the comments down
below if not someone going with me we're
gonna make a fortune doing strawberry
banana energy drinks I guess I should
taste that one first or I should taste
this one
first hmm we're back to tasting like a
healthy fruit vegetable juice
it's definitely got the hint of peach
and mango definitely get that fruit
juice vegetable juice flavor to it if
you guys wanna know what I mean by the
fruit juice vegetable flavor here's what
I mean it tastes like fruit juice
vegetable juice and how do I explain
that I mean is that healthy vegetable
fruit juice flavor I don't know how to
describe it you know how to tell you go
ahead and buy some v8 energy and you'll
know what fruit juice vegetable juice
tastes like actually these probably
taste like the v8 fusion just we
caffeine since I never buy me a fusion I
wouldn't know if you drink v8 fusion and
you think they taste like this comment
down below how many times can I tell you
guys to comment down below I can't even
keep up with all the comments lately
I mean it's nuts I actually looked up to
see how many VA energy drinks were done
for reviews that was a decent amount I
said oh man I'm gonna have to compete
against all those but away you guys
comment I'll I'll boot them right up
that list I'm off topic again I'm moving
on to the next one I'm still aching a
pomegranate blueberry a little bit
better and hoping for the best
strawberry banana next up if you
couldn't have guessed strawberry banana
and that is relatively delicious I made
the right choice saving the best for
last
I felt strawberry banana was gonna be
the best out of the five I was right for
a change it still has a little bit that
vegetable fruit juice taste to it but it
really reminds me more of like a
smoothie if you ever had yourself a
strawberry banana smoothie then you had
all those other things to it to make it
healthy like you're puttin that
spirulina snuck in some broccoli it
snuck in some kale mixed it all up in
there
to make sure you go all your healthy
stuff and your smoothie if you covered
it up with strawberry and banana
flavoring so you couldn't taste all
those vegetables that's what this is
right here
it's your strongest favorite flavors
strawberry and banana covering up all
that other healthy stuff smart movie
eight I'm having another healthy sip so
overall if you guys are looking to get
yourselves a healthy energy drink and I
mean super healthy energy drink these
things are your typical energy drinks
they're really just a really healthy
drink but they
caffeine too and some other vitamins so
if you like v8 you like fruit juices you
like tomato juices you like all that
juicy kind of stuff and you want to get
a little extra energy these are gonna be
great for you if you're a gamer who
drinks the game Fuel Mountain Dew Red
Bull amp spike or any of those other
hardcore energy drinks stay away from
the VA energy you're not gonna like it
you can only unsubscribe to my channel
or something because you're gonna find
them super disgusting and they're not
super disgusting but because you like my
own dude you're probably gonna think
they're disgusting
so I know my videos are for different
target audiences I got my gamers and I
got my healthy people and a lot of those
energy drinks sometimes crossover these
do not so if you're interested in buying
these I'll include a link to Amazon down
below but the truth is I mean you can
pick these up anywhere I'm gonna go
there at Target they're probably have
plenty of other grocery stores as well
but if you like Amazon feel free to use
the link I provided down below I'm an
Amazon affiliate so I'll make a very
very small Commission for my repurchase
but hey every little bit helps me out
because after five weeks of waiting to
be accepted into the YouTube Partner
Program I'm still waiting but I'm not
complaining that's all I got for you so
hopefully I'll see you guys next Tuesday
I'm probably gonna be reviewing
something very very very unhealthy but
he's after drinking those I need to get
some sugar in my system I need to do
something uh-huh well I just happen to
have one of these right here
what pedal wait over washdown some fruit
juice then with a real energy drink so
until next Tuesday you guys have
yourself a great day or night to shake
these first
do they say shake do or say shake first
please no I want to shake it if you're
going to explode yeah doesn't say maybe
I'll just tip it okay
you